<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Muhamad Fajar</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/</link><description>Recent content on Muhamad Fajar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 18:30:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://muhfajar.blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating a New Theme</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 16:08:01 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 17:32:59 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</guid><description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description></item><item><title>Modern Problems Require Modern Solutions</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/modern-problems-require-modern-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 15:55:14 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/modern-problems-require-modern-solutions/</guid><description>Recently I posted about my experience with the longest work from home (posted in Bahasa) I ever had so far. The biggest challenge about work from home on the internet era is an internet connection itself. I often got a bad connection in the middle of the meeting, that not good especially I&amp;rsquo;m the host in a meeting, not only once but &amp;ldquo;daily standup meeting&amp;rdquo;. Yes, you can see daily in the quoted word.</description></item><item><title>Purge Cache with Git Hooks</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/purge-cache-with-git-hooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 11:22:17 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/purge-cache-with-git-hooks/</guid><description>In the last post about deploying Now with Cloudflare, I have been describing in general how to deploy a project using Now and how to integrating with Cloudflare. After success deploying, if you set Cloudflare cache to make your website faster I guess you will face issue relate with a cache.
First, if you push or make changes, your website not instantly follow the changes. From my experience that because of cache!</description></item><item><title>Deploying Now With Cloudflare</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/deploying-now-with-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 04:52:59 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/deploying-now-with-cloudflare/</guid><description>:: this post has been updated with the latest update from Vercel (formerly ZEIT) I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with Now deployment for a few months. First I thought about Now is magic, with only small configuration (in v2) I can deploy a static website easily and with the latest update, now I can deploy (with default template) any static website without any configuration. That&amp;rsquo;s amazing.
How to Deploy First thing, you need Vercel account, of course.</description></item></channel></rss>