<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tech on Muhamad Fajar</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/categories/tech/</link><description>Recent content in tech on Muhamad Fajar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 11:22:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://muhfajar.blog/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Purge Cache with Git Hooks</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/purge-cache-with-git-hooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 11:22:17 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/purge-cache-with-git-hooks/</guid><description>In the last post about deploying Now with Cloudflare, I have been describing in general how to deploy a project using Now and how to integrating with Cloudflare. After success deploying, if you set Cloudflare cache to make your website faster I guess you will face issue relate with a cache.
First, if you push or make changes, your website not instantly follow the changes. From my experience that because of cache!</description></item><item><title>Deploying Now with Cloudflare</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/deploying-now-with-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 04:52:59 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/deploying-now-with-cloudflare/</guid><description>:: this post has been updated with the latest update from Vercel (formerly ZEIT) I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with Now deployment for a few months. First I thought about Now is magic, with only small configuration (in v2) I can deploy a static website easily and with the latest update, now I can deploy (with default template) any static website without any configuration. That&amp;rsquo;s amazing.
How to Deploy First thing, you need Vercel account, of course.</description></item><item><title>Playing in Ruby Mine</title><link>https://muhfajar.blog/playing-in-ruby-mine/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 12:52:59 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://muhfajar.blog/playing-in-ruby-mine/</guid><description>I started as Ruby dev in my new job, previously I worked as PHP and Python dev and I found Ruby is slightly different sometimes especially with PHP. First time I read Ruby documentation, Ruby syntax is familiar, that looks like Python with some additional word every end of a function. For example:
def foo(): print(&amp;#39;bar&amp;#39;) def foo puts &amp;#39;bar&amp;#39; end For framework Ruby have Rails (not only Rails actually, many framework out there) and when I came to my new job, I have only 3 days to learn what Ruby is and what is Rails, so basically I am learning by doing after my quick learn from digging up Ruby and Rails documentation.</description></item></channel></rss>